{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
  {
    "category": "History",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "The Kingdom of Prussia briefly held land in Estonia.",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "True"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "In the comic book &quot;Archie&quot;, Betty is friends with Veronica because she is rich.",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "True"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Science & Nature",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "It was once believed that injecting shark cartilage into people would prevent them from contracting cancer.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "The fourth funnel of the RMS Titanic was fake designed to make the ship look more powerful and symmetrical.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "The Battle of Trafalgar took place on October 23rd, 1805",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "True"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Music",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "The band STRFKR was also briefly known as Pyramiddd.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Science & Nature",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "The value of one Calorie is different than the value of one calorie.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Stagecoach owned &quot;South West Trains&quot; before losing the rights to FirstGroup and MTR in March of 2017.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Film",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "The weapon Clint Eastwood uses in &quot;Dirty Harry&quot; was a .44 Automag.",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "True"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "In the &quot;To Love-Ru&quot; series, Peke is considered a female robot.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "False"
    ]
  }
]
}